邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
萨姆
Sammy.
尽快把你弟弟带出屋去 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can. Go.
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
而且已经好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
这是爸爸的笔记
This is Dad's book.
我觉得他希望我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
猎杀恶鬼 拯救人们
You know, saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
The family business.
我要找到爸爸
I gotta find Dad.
这才是我最想做的事
It's the only thing I can think about.
此刻我即将入睡
Now I lay me down to sleep...
我祈求上帝保佑我的灵魂
l pray the Lord my soul to keep.
愿天使整晚守护着我
Thy angels watch me through the night.
让我安睡到明日曙光
And keep me safe till morning light.
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
晚安 小捣蛋
Good night, monkey-puss.
爸爸
Daddy...
妈妈回来了吗？
is Mommy coming home?
还没有 亲爱的
No, honey.
她要在医院陪你姐姐
She's spending the night at the hospital with your sister.
嘿
Hey.
现在好好睡
You sleep tight, now.
《邪恶力量》
你肯定漏下了什么没查
Yeah. You probably missed something, that's what.
我查了律商联讯数据库 当地警局报告
Dude, I ran LexisNexis, local police records, newspapers.
报纸 找不到任何奇怪的事情
I couldn't find a single red flag.
你确定你找对了坐标吗？
Are you sure you got the coordinates right?
对 我反复查过了 就是在威斯康星州的费区堡
Yeah. l double-checked.It's Fitchburg, Wisconsin.
萨姆 要是这坐标不重要的话 父亲不会把它传给我们的
Dad wouldn't have sent coordinates if it wasn't important.
那我告诉你 结果什么都没有 我彻底查过了
I'm telling you, I looked. All l found was a big, steamy pile of nothing.
要是父亲要我们来猎杀什么东西的话 我可不知道是什么
If Dad's sending us hunting for something, l don't know what.
也许他会在那和我们碰头 是啊
- Maybe he'll meet us there. - Yeah.
没错 因为他很容易就可以被找到
Because he's been so easy to find up to this point.
你真是个自作聪明的家伙
You're a real smart-ass, you know that?
别担心
Don't worry.
我肯定费区堡有什么值得我们去猎杀的
I'm sure there's something in Fitchburg worth killing.
是吗？你怎么那么肯定？
Yeah? What makes you so sure?
因为我比你大 所以我说的都是对的
Well, because I'm the oldest, which means l'm always right.
- 才不是那样 - 就是这样
- No, it doesn't. - it totally does.
好…
Well...
里面的女侍应说
the waitress thinks
当地的美生会在进行一些神秘的活动
that the local Freemasons are up to something sneaky...
除此之外 没人有听说发生过任何奇怪的事情
but other than that, nobody's heard about anything weird going on.
迪恩 几点了？
Dean, you got the time?
4点10分
Ten after 4.
怎么？
Why?
那场景有什么奇怪吗？
What's wrong with this picture?
已经放学了 对吧？
School's out, isn't it?
没错
Yeah.
人都哪去了？
So where is everybody?
这种时候这里应该到处是玩耍的小孩的
This place should be crawling with kids right now.
这可真安静啊
Sure is quiet out here.
没错 太可惜了
Yeah. lt's a shame.
- 怎么会这样？- 孩子们都病了
- Why's that? - You know, kids getting sick.
真是太可怕了
It's a terrible thing.
有多少孩子病了？
How many?
只有五六个 可是病得很严重
Just five or six, but serious.
要住院
Hospital serious.
很多父母都变的很担心
A lot of parents are getting pretty anxious.
他们觉得是什么传染病
They think it's catching.
嘿 哥们 我才不用这个身份
Dude. Dude, l am not using this lD.
- 为什么？- 因为上面写着"比基尼观察员"
- Why not? - Because it says "bikini inspector" on it.
别担心 她不会检查那么仔细的
Don't worry. She won't look that close
她可能根本不会要求看身份证明的
Hell, she won't even ask to see it.
这只关乎自信的事 萨姆
It's all about confidence, Sammy.
嗨 我是疾病控制中心的杰里·卡普兰医生
Hi. l'm Doctor Jerry Kaplan, Center for Disease Control.
我可以看下身份证明吗？
Can l see some lD?
当然可以
Yeah, of course.
能告诉我儿科监控室怎么走吗？
Now, could you direct me to the pediatrics ward, please?
好的 穿过大厅 左转 再上楼梯就到了
Well, just go down the hall.Turn left. Up the stairs.
看吧 告诉你这招有用的
See? Told you it'd work.
跟我来 在楼上
Follow me. It's upstairs.
迪恩
Dean
谢谢你能抽空见我们下海德克尔医生
Thanks for seeing us, Dr. Heidecker.
噢 我很高兴你们能过来一趟
Well, l'm glad you guys are here.
我正打算要打电话给疾病控制中心
I was just about to call CDC myself.
你们是怎么发现的？
How'd you find out, anyway?
一个叫G. -P. -的人 我忘记名字了
Oh, some G.P. l forget his name.
他打电话到了亚特兰大 一定抢在你们之前了
He called Atlanta and must've beat you to the punch.
所以说到现在这已经有6个病例了
So you say you've got six cases so far?
对 5周之内出现了6例
Yeah, yeah. Five weeks.
起初我以为是什么病菌引起的肺炎
At first, we thought it was garden variety bacterial pneumonia.
没什么值得紧张的
Not newsworthy.
可是现在…
But now...
现在怎么了？
Now what?
孩子们对抗菌素没什么反映
The kids aren't responding to antibiotics.
而白细胞数量在持续降低
Their white cell counts keep going down.
他们的免疫系统都没起什么作用
Their immune systems just aren't doing their job.
就好象他们的身体机能都瘫痪了
It's like their bodies are wearing out.
打扰一下 海德克尔医生 你以前有看过这样的病例吗？
Excuse me, Dr. Heidecker? - Ever see anything like this before?
没这么严重的
Never this severe.
这种传染的方式 我还是头一次看到
The way it spreads, that's a new one for me.
- 什么意思？- 这病以家庭为单位传染
- What do you mean? - lt works its way through families...
可是只传染儿童 兄弟姐妹一个接着一个病倒
but only the children, one sibling after another.
能不能让我们和其中几个孩子谈下？
You mind if we interview a few of the kids?
他们都还在昏迷中
They're not conscious.
- 全都昏迷了？- 对
- None of them? - No.
我们能和病人的父母谈会吗？
Can we-? Can we talk to the parents?
要是你觉得能起帮助的话
If you think it'll help.
最近的一个病例是谁？
Yeah, yeah. Who was your most recent admission?
我得回去陪我的女儿们
I should get back to my girls.
我们了解 我们很感激你能告诉我们到底发生了什么
We understand that, and we really appreciate you talking to us.
你说玛丽是你的大女儿？
Now, you say Mary's the oldest?
13岁
- Thirteen.
她先开始病倒的 对吧？
She came down with it first, right?
- 接着… - 贝瑟尼第二个晚上也病倒了
- And then - Bethany, the next night.
24小时之内吗？
Within 24 hours?
我猜是的
I guess.
听着 我已经把所有的事情都和医生说了
Look, l already went through all this with the doctor.
如果你不介意的话 只剩下几个问题了
Right. Now, just a few more questions, if you don't mind.
你觉得她们怎么会得肺炎？
How do you think they caught pneumonia?
她们有着凉或是什么吗？
Were they out in the cold? Anything like that?
我们觉得都是因为窗户都打开了 两次都是吗？
- No, we think it was an open window. - Both times?
第一次我不太记得了
The first time, l don't I don't really remember.
第二次肯定打开了
But the second time for sure.
可是我记得贝瑟尼睡觉前我明明关好了？
l closed it before l put Bethany to bed
所以你觉得是她打开的
So you think she opened it?
那是没边框的二楼窗户
It's a second-story window, no ledge.
别人不可能能打开
No one else could have.
这可能并不是什么灵异事件
You know, this might not be anything supernatural.
可能只是肺炎而已 可能
- Might just be pneumonia. - Maybe.
也可能是什么东西打开的窗户
Or maybe something opened that window.
我不知道 老弟 可是父亲叫我们到这来一定有他的原因
I don't know.Dad sent us here for a reason.
- 我想我们可能找到原因了 - 有件事我要告诉你
- l think we're barking up the right tree. - l'll tell you one thing.
- 什么？- 刚刚和我们谈过的那个男人
- What? - That guy we just talked to...
我打赌他暂时还不会回家去
l'm betting it'll be a while before he goes home.
你那有找到什么吗？
You got anything over there?
什么也没有
No, nothing.
我这也是
Yeah, me neither.
- 嘿 迪恩 - 什么？
- Hey, Dean? - Yeah.
你说的没错
You were right.
这不是什么肺炎
It's not pneumonia.
都已经腐坏了
It's rotted.
什么鬼东西会留下这样的手印？
What the hell leaves a handprint like that?
好了
All right.
你知道规矩的 迪恩 任何人打电话过来都不要接
You know the drill, Dean.Anybody calls, you don't pick up.
如果是我打的 我只会响一次 然后再打过来
If it's me, I'll ring once and then call back.
知道了吗？
You got that?
恩 除非是只响一次的电话 不然不要接
Don't answer the phone unless it rings once first.
来吧 伙计 认真点 这很重要
Come on, dude. Look alive.This stuff's important.
我知道 只是
I know. It's just...
我们之前已经做过无数次了 你知道我并不笨
we've gone over it, like, a million times, and you know I'm not stupid.
我知道你不笨 可是一点错都不能犯 知道了吗？
I know you're not, but it only takes one mistake. You got that?
那好 要是我周日晚上还没回来的话…
All right, if l'm not back Sunday night
打电话给吉姆牧师
Call Pastor Jim.
锁好门窗 关好窗帘
Lock the doors, the windows.Close the shades.
- 最重要的是 - 照看好萨姆
- And most important - Watch out for Sammy.
- 我知道 - 好吧
- l know. - All right.
- 要是有什么企图闯进屋… - 先开枪 然后再问问题
- Something tries to bust in? - Shoot first, ask questions later.
这才是我的儿子
That's my man.
我知道父亲为什么叫我们来这了
I know why Dad sent us here.
他以前碰到过它
He's faced this thing before.
他想让我们来完结这事
He wants us to finish the job.
Shtriga到底是什么玩意？
So, what the hell is a Shtriga?
我觉得是某种象女巫之类的 我并不了解多少
It's kind of like a witch, I think.They don't know that much about them.
我可从来没听说过 而且也没出现在父亲的日记里
I've never heard of it, and it's not in Dad's journal.
父亲在威斯康星州的福特道格拉斯曾经猎杀过一个
Dad hunted one in Fort Douglas, Wisconsin
大概在16 17年前
about 16, 17 years ago.
- 你当时也在 不记得了吗？- 不记得
- You were there. You don't remember? - No.
我猜他有听到风声说在费区堡又出现了
Guess he caught wind it's in Fitchburg
所以才给我们这个坐标
and kicked us the coordinates.
- 这么说来 这个 - Shtriga. -
- So wait, this... - Shtriga.
对 你认为就是父亲曾经猎杀过的那个吗？
Right. You think it's the same one Dad hunted before?
很有可能
Yeah, maybe.
要是父亲已经猎杀过了 为什么现在它还没消失？
If Dad went after it, why is it still breathing air?
- 因为当时它跑了 - 跑了？
- Because it got away. - Got away?
- 对 萨姆 这种事发生过 - 可不是经常能发生
- Yeah, Sammy. lt happens. - Not very often.
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know what to tell you.
也许父亲只是那天失手了而已
Maybe Dad didn't have his Wheaties that morning.
你还记得什么？
What else do you remember?
没有了 我当时也只是个孩子而已 记得吗？
Nothing. l was a kid, all right?
单人间还是双人间？
King or two queens?
双人间
Two queens.
- 我猜也是 - 你说什么？
- Yeah, I bet. - What'd you say?
车不错. -
Nice car.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 要入住吗？- 对
- Checking in? - Yeah.
帮忙去拿点你弟弟的食物
Do me a favor, go get your brother some dinner.
我正在招待客人呢
I'm helping a guest.
双人间
Two queens.
有趣的孩子 没错 他也那么觉得
- Funny kid.Oh, yeah. He thinks so.
- 付现金还是用信用卡？- 能用万事达信用卡吗？
- Will that be cash or credit? - You take MasterCard?
太好了 给你
Perfect. Here you go.
爸爸什么时候回来？
When's Dad gonna get back?
明天
Tomorrow.
- 明天什么时候？- 我不知道
- When? - l don't know.
通常来说会很晚回来
He usually comes in late, though.
来 开始吃饭吧
Now, eat your dinner.
我已经吃厌Scabetti牌的麦片了
I'm sick of "scabetti-ohs."
是你自己要吃的
Well, you're the one who wanted them.
我想吃Lucky Charms牌的麦片
I want Lucky Charms.
- 已经没有Lucky Charms了 - 我看到盒子了
- There's no more Lucky Charms. - l saw the box.
可能还剩点
Okay, maybe there is.
可是也只够你一个人吃的 我什么都还没吃
But there's only enough left for one bowl, and l haven't had any yet.
你要这个奖品吗？
Do you want the prize?
先生？
Sir?
谢谢
Thanks.
你说的没错
Well, you were right.
尽管很难找到 可你说的没错
It wasn't very easy to find, but you were right.
Shtriga是一种女巫
A Shtriga is a kind of witch.
来自阿尔巴尼亚
They're Albanian
可是有关它们的传说要追溯到古罗马时代
but legends about them date back to ancient Rome.
它们以精神能量为食
They need off of spiritus vitae.
- 精神是什么？- Vitae
- Spirit what? - Vitae.
意思是"生命能源"
It's Latin. Translates to "breath of life."
类似生命能量或是精华之类
Kind of like your life force or essence.
医生不是说那些孩子的身体机能都瘫痪了吗？
Didn't the doctor say the kids' bodies were wearing out?
只是种想法而已 它吸走了你的能量
It's a thought. She takes your vitality
你的免疫功能就丧失了
maybe your immunity goes to hell.
然后才会患上肺炎
Pneumonia takes hold.
不管怎样 Shtrigas的猎物可以是任何人
Anyway, Shtrigas can feed off anyone.
- 不过它们更喜欢 - 小孩
- But they prefer-Children.
对
Yeah.
可能是因为小孩子有更强的生命能量 听听这些
Probably because they have stronger life force. And get this
Shtrigas对神和人制造出的 任何武器都免疫
"Shtrigas are invulnerable to all weapons devised by God and man."
不是那样的
No. That's not right.
当它们进食的时候 并不是免疫的
She's vulnerable when she feeds.
什么？
What?
如果你正好抓到它正在进食的话
If you catch her while eating
就能用神圣的子弹消灭它
you can blast her with consecrated wrought iron.
大号铅弹或者是铁弹之类的
Buckshots or rounds,
- 你怎么知道这些？- 父亲告诉过我 我还记得
- How do you know that? - Dad told me. I remember.
哦
Oh.
那么父亲还有提及别的什么的吗？
So anything else Dad might've mentioned?
没有 就这些了
No, that's it.
什么？
What?
没什么
Nothing.
那好
Okay.
所以我们假设在它进食的时候可以消灭它
So assuming we can kill it when it eats
我们还是得先找到它
we still gotta find the thing first...
这并不是什么容易的事
which aingt gonna be a cakewalk.
Shtrigas不猎食的时候伪装成人的样子
Shtrigas take a human disguise when they're not hunting.
- 什么样的伪装？- 有史可稽 它们会装成无害的样子
- What kind of human disguise? - Historically, something innocuous.
可以是任何人 不过一般伪装成衰弱的老妇
Anything, but it's usually a feeble old woman...
也许这就是那些老巫婆传说的由来
which may be how the whole witches-as-old-crones legend got started.
- 等等 - 怎么？
- Hang on. - What?
看看这个 我标记了所有受害者的地址
Check this out. I marked down all the addresses of the victims.
这些房子之间相距甚远
These are the houses that have been hit so far.
但都围绕着
And dead center...
医院
The hospital.
我们上午在医院的时候 我有看到一位病人 一位老妇
When we were there, I saw a patient, an old woman.
- 一位老人 - 对
- An old person, huh? - Yeah.
在医院吗？
In the hospital?
呼 是时候叫海卫队了
Whoo. Better call the coast guard.
听着 你这自以为是的家伙 她墙上有个倒十字
Listen, smart-ass. She had an inverted cross hanging on her wall.
- 晚安 海德克尔医生 - 明天见 贝蒂
- Good night, Doctor HayDecker. - See you, Betty.
试着睡会
Try to get some sleep.
你是谁？
Who the hell are you?
谁在哪？
Who's there?
你想偷我的东西吗？
You're trying to steal my stuff?
这附近老有小偷
They're always stealing around here.
不是的 女士 我们是维修工人 很抱歉吓到你
No, madam, we're maintenance.We're sorry.
我们以为你睡着了
We thought you were sleeping.
胡扯 我可是睁着只眼睡觉的
Nonsense. l was sleeping with my peepers open.
可以顺便修下那个十字架吗？
And fix that crucifix, would you?
我已经叫过四次让人来修了
I've asked four damn times already.
"我可是睁着只眼睡觉的"
"I was sleeping with my peepers open"?
我差点就真的开枪了 我发誓
I almost smoked that old gal, I swear.
并不好笑
It's not funny.
你真该看看你当时的表情 迪恩
Oh, man. You should've seen your face, Dean.
尽管笑吧 我们又回到起点了
Oh, yeah. Laugh it up.We're back to square one.
等会
Hang on.
嘿 怎么回事？
Hey. What's wrong?
我弟弟病了
My brother's sick.
那个小家伙？
The little guy?
肺炎
Pneumonia.
他住院了
He's in the hospital.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
不是你的错 怎么回事？
Oh, come on. How?
我该查看下窗户有没关好
I should have made sure the window was latched.
要是窗户关好了 他就不会得肺炎了
He wouldn't have got pneumonia if the window was latched.
听我说
Listen to me.
我向你保证这一切都不是你的错
I can promise you that this is not your fault.
好吗？
Okay?
照看他是我的职责
It's my job to look after him.
迈克尔
Michael
我走了之后挂上"停止营业"的牌子
Turn on the "no vacancy" sign while l'm gone.
我叫丹尼斯来负责客房服务了 所以别担心客房的事
l've got Denise covering room service.So don't worry about the room
我和你一起去
l'm going with you.
- 现在不行迈克尔 - 我得去看看阿舍
- Not now, Michael. - But l gotta see Asher.
嘿 迈克尔
Hey, Michael.
嘿 我知道你现在的感觉 我也是当兄长的
Hey. I know how you feel, okay? I'm a big brother too...
可是你现在不能再让你母亲分心 对吧？
but you gotta go easy on your mom right now, okay?
- 该死 - 我来拣
- Damn it. - l got it.
谢谢
Thanks.
你这个样子不能开车 我送你去医院吧
You're in no condition to drive.Let me give you a lift.
不 不 我不能那么
- No, I couldn't possibly-No, it's no trouble. l insist.
不 不麻烦 我送你吧
Thanks.
乖点
Be good.
我们一定要消灭它 一定要消灭它 听清楚了吗？
We're gonna kill this thing.I want it dead, you hear me?
- 嘿 - 嘿 孩子怎么样了？
- Hey. - Hey. How's the kid?
不怎么好 你在哪？我在图书馆里
- He's not good. Where you at? - I'm at the library.
看能不能找到更多这个Shtriga的资料
Trying to find out as much as l can about this Shtriga.
- 找到什么没有？- 坏消息. -
- Yeah, what do you got? - Well, bad news.
我从你说父亲在福特道格拉斯 那时开始着手
I started with-With Fort Douglas, around the time you said Dad was there.
- 然后呢？- 一样的状况
- And? - Same deal.
在那之前 还在奥格登市出现过
Before that, there was There was Ogdenville.
另外之前还有北溪哈弗和布罗克韦
before that, North Haverbrook and Brockway.
每15到20年 它就袭击一个新的城镇
Every 15 to 20 years it hits a new town.
迪恩 它在菲奇堡只是刚刚开始而已
Dean, this thing is just getting started in Fitchburg.
在其他地方 在它最终消失前 它的猎食要持续几个月
In all these other places, it goes on for months...
要殃及很多孩子
dozens of kids before the Shtriga finally moves on.
那些孩子只是持续昏厥 然后再死去
Kids just languish in comas and then they die.
最远能追溯到什么时候？我不知道
- How far back does this thing go? - I don't know.
我能找到最早提及的是在1890年代
Earliest mention I could find was this place called Black River Falls...
叫做黑色瀑布的地方
back in the 1890s.
简直就是在看一部恐怖秀
Talk about a horror show.
哇
Whoa.
萨姆？
Sam?
等会 我正在看着一张图片
Hold on. I'm looking at a photograph right now of a bunch of doctors...
上面有一群医生站在一个孩子的床边
standing around a kid's bed.
其中有个医生就是海德克尔
One of the doctors is Heidecker.
然后呢？这张照片是在1893年照的
- And? - And this picture was taken in 1893.
你确定吗？确定
- You're sure? - Yeah.
很确定
Yeah, absolutely.
别担心
Don't worry.
你的儿子不会出什么事
Your son's in good hands.
我会好好照顾他的
I'm gonna take care of him.
疾病控制中心到现在有什么进展吗？
So, what's the CDC come up with so far?
我们还在研究一些理论
We're still working on a few theories.
我们一有消息就马上通知你
You'll know something as soon as we do.
这些孩子对我来说比什么都重要
Well, nothing's more important to me than these kids.
有什么要帮忙的地方尽管提
Just let me know if I can help.
我会的
I'll do that.
我们之前就应该想到了 医生正是极好的伪装
We should have thought of this before.A doctor's a perfect disguise.
人们信任医生 正好可以掌控大局
You're trusted.You can control the whole thing.
那个混蛋
That son of a bitch.
我纳闷你当时怎么不对他动手
I'm surprised you didn't draw on him right there.
恩 …
Yeah, well...
首先 我才不会在儿科监控室开枪
first of all, I'm not gonna open fire in a frigging pediatrics ward.
- 好理由 - 第二 根本起不到什么作用
- Good call. - Second, it wouldn't have done any good.
那混蛋对子弹免疫 除非他正在猎食中
The bastard's bulletproof unless he's chowing down on something.
另外 我身上没装备 说起来这样真算便宜了他
And third, I wasn't packing, which is probably a really good thing...
否则我就会不顾什么原则
because I probably would've just burned a clip in him
上去赏他几个耳光
off the principle alone.
- 长大了才变聪明 迪恩 - 你说的没错
- You're getting wise in your old age. - You're damn right.
因为我知道我们现在该怎么做了
Because now I know how we're gonna get it.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
- 那个Shtriga它以兄弟姐妹为猎物对吧？- 没错
- The Shtriga works through siblings? - Right.
- 那么 昨天晚上… - 它袭击了Asher
- Well, last night-lt went after Asher.
所以今天晚上可能会来袭击Michael
Tonight it's gonna come after Michael.
我们得马上把他带离这里
Then we gotta get him out of here.
不 那样只会坏掉整个计划 什么？
- No, that would blow the whole deal. - What?
- 是啊 - 你想拿那孩子当诱饵？
- Yeah. - Then you wanna use the kid as bait?
你是不是疯了？别想了 这不可能会成功的
Are you nuts? No. Forget it.That's out of the question.
不不不 萨姆 这是唯一的机会
No no no sam, It's the only way.
要是它再消失了 可能要再等很多年才会有下一次机会
If this thing disappears, it could be years before we get a chance.
迈克尔只是个孩子而已 我才不会让他面对那鬼玩意
Michael is child, I'm not gonna dangle him in front
就象钓钩上的鱼饵一样
of that thing like a worm on a hook.
父亲叫我到这来 不是叫我什么也不干的
Dad did not send me here to walk away.
他不只叫你到这来
Send you here? He didn't send you here, he sent us here.
他是叫我们到这来 这根本不管你的事情 萨姆
This isn't about you, Sam.
我是搞砸事情的人
I'm the one that screwed up.
都是我的错 都是因为我
It's my fault. There's no telling how many kids
才会有这么多的孩子 受到伤害
have gotten hurt because of me.
你在说什么 迪恩？
What are you saying, Dean?
这怎么会是你的错？
How is it your fault?
迪恩…
Dean.
关于这Shtriga 你有什么事情瞒着我
you've been hiding something from the get-go.
从什么时候父亲开始猎杀失败？
Since when does Dad bail on a hunt?
从什么时候他开始让什么鬼怪逃走了？
Since when does he let something get away?
告诉我
Now, talk to me, man.
告诉我到底发生了什么
Tell me what's going on.
在威斯康星州道格拉斯堡
Fort Douglas Wisconsin
那是在那个破烂的房子的第三个晚上
It was the third night in this crap room...
我当时出了门 我需要呼吸点新鲜空气
and I was climbing the walls, man.I needed to get some air.
嘿 孩子
Kid.
我们要关门了
We're closing up.
让开
Get out of the way!
萨姆
Sammy.
萨姆 萨姆
Sammy. Sammy.
- 你没事吧？- 爸爸 怎么回事？
- You okay? - Dad, what's going on?
你没事吧？
You all right?
- 发生什么了？- 我刚出去了下
- What happened? - l just went out.
- 什么？- 我只出去了一会 我很抱歉
- What? - Just for a second. l'm sorry.
我告诉过你不许离开房间
I told you not to leave this room.
我告诉过你不要让他离开你的视线
I told you not to let him out of your sight.
父亲只是带上我们
Dad just grabbed us and booked.
花了三个小时把我们放到吉姆牧师那
Dropped us off at Pastor Jim's about three hours away.
等他回到道格拉斯堡的时候 那个Shtriga已经消失了
By the time he got back to Fort Douglas, the Shtriga disappeared.
就那么消失了
It was lt was just gone.
直到现在才又再出现
It never resurfaced until now.
父亲从此再也没提起那件事
You know, Dad never spoke about it again.
我也从没问过
I didn't ask.
可是他 呃…
But he...
他对待我也不同了
He looked at me different, you know?
对我来说那是更糟的事
Which was worse.
我不会责怪他
Not that l blamed him.
他给我下的命令 我没有遵守 而且我差点让你被杀
He gave me an order, and l didn't listen. I almost got you killed.
- 你只是个孩子而已 - 别那么说
- You were just a kid. - Don't.
别
Don't.
父亲知道对我来说这是我要完成的工作
Dad knew this was unfinished business for me.
他叫我来消灭它的
He sent me here to finish it.
可是利用迈克尔
But using Michael...
我不知道 迪恩
I don't know, Dean.
我是说 不如我们其中一个藏在被子下
I mean, how about one of us hides under the cover, you know?
让我们做诱饵
We'll be the bait.
不 不会有用的
No, it won't work.
要贴的足够近它才能够进食 它会发现我们的
It's gotta get close enough to feed.It'll see us.
相信我 我也不喜欢这样 可是只能让那孩子来当诱饵
Believe me, l don't like it, but it's gotta be the kid.
你一定是疯了 快点走开 不然我就要叫警察了
You're crazy. Just go away, or l'm calling the cops.
先挂一下 听我说
Hang on a second. Just listen to me.
你一定要相信我 好吗？
You have to believe me, okay?
那鬼怪从窗户爬进来 袭击了你的弟弟
This thing came through the window, and it attacked your brother.
我看到过
I've seen it.
我知道这听起来是什么感觉
I know what it looks like...
因为之前它也袭击我弟弟一次
because it attacked my brother once too.
这个鬼怪 它看起来…
This thing, is it, like...?
它穿着长长的黑袍？
It has this long, black robe?
你昨晚也看到了 对吧？
You saw it last night, didn't you?
我以为我做了个噩梦
I thought I was having a nightmare.
虽然不情愿告诉你这些
I'd give anything not to tell you this...
不过有的时候噩梦也能成真
but sometimes nightmares are real.
- 那为什么要告诉我这些？- 因为我们需要你的帮助
- So why are you telling me? - Because we need your help.
我的帮助？
My help?
我们可以消灭它 我们两个 这正是我们一直在干的事
We can kill it, me and him, it's what we do.
可是没有你的帮忙我们做不到
But we can't do it without you.
什么？不行
What? No.
迈克尔听我说
Michael, listen to me.
那鬼怪袭击了阿舍
This thing hurt Asher...
要是我们不阻止它 它还会继续袭击其他的孩子？
and it's gonna keep hurting kids unless we stop it.
你听懂了吗
Do you understand me?
进行得不顺利
Well, that went crappy.
- 现在怎么办？- 你在期许什么？
- Now what? - What did you expect?
即使叫个成年人来做这种事情也不可能
You can't ask an adult to do something like that
更别说是小孩子了
much less a kid.
要是你们消灭了它 阿舍会好起来吗？
If you kill it, will Asher get better?
老实说 我们也不知道
Honestly, we don't know.
你说过你也是做哥哥的对吧？
You said you're a big brother.
对
Yeah.
你会一直照顾好你弟弟的？
You'd take care of your little brother?
你会为他做点事情的对吧？
You'd do anything for him?
是的 我会的
Yeah, l would.
我也是
Me too.
我会帮忙的
I'll help.
这种相机有夜视功能
This camera has night vision on it
所以我们可以象白天一样看你看得很清楚
so we'll be able to see as clear as day.
怎么样？头发也能看清楚. -
- Are we good? - Hair to the right.
好了 好了
There, there.
我要做些什么？
What do l do?
只要躲在被窝里就好
Just stay under the covers.
要是它出现了呢？
And if it shows up?
我们就在旁边的房间 我们会带着枪冲进来
Well, we'll be right in the next room. We're gonna come in with guns.
等我们一冲进来 你就滚下床 藏到床底下去
So, soon as we do, you roll off this bed and you crawl under it.
要是你们打到我怎么办？
What if you shoot me?
我们不会伤到你的 我们枪法很准
We won't shoot you. We're good shots.
等你安全之后我们才会开枪的
We're not gonna fire until you're clear, okay?
- 你以前有听过枪声吗？- 就象电影里面的一样吗？
- Have you heard a gunshot before? - Like in the movies?
比电影里面的声音要大一点
It's gonna be a lot louder than in the movies.
所以我希望你躲在床底下 掩住耳朵
So l want you to stay under the bed...
我们叫你出来之前别出来 懂了吗？
cover your ears, and do not come out until we say so, you understand?
Michael 你确定你要这样做吗？
Michael, you sure you wanna do this?
你没必要那么做 没事的 我不会生气
You don't have to, it's okay.I won't be mad.
不 我没事 只要你别向我开枪
No, I'm okay. Just don't shoot me.
我们不会让你发生任何事
We're not gonna let anything happen to you.
我保证
Promise.
现在什么时候了？
What time is it?
3点
It's 3.
你确定这些铁弹会有用吗？
You sure these iron rounds are gonna work?
神圣的铁弹 上次父亲就是用的这些
Consecrated iron rounds.And, yeah, it's what Dad used last time.
嘿 迪恩 我很抱歉
Hey, Dean, l'm sorry.
为什么抱歉？
For what?
你知道的…
You know...
我一直嘲笑你 总是听父亲的命令
l've really given you a lot of crap for always following Dad's orders.
- 现在我知道你为什么那么做了 - 天啊 杀了我吧
- But l know why you do it. - Oh, God. Kill me now.
等等 看
Wait, look.
- 现在吗？- 还没
- Now? - Not yet.
迈克尔 低下
Hey! Michael, down!
- 迈克你没事吧？- 没事
- Mike, you all right? - Yeah.
别动
Just sit tight.
迪恩
Dean!
嘿
Hey!
你没事吧 老弟？
You okay, little brother?
没事了 迈克尔 你可以出来了
It's okay, Michael.You can come on out.
- 嘿 乔安娜 阿舍怎么样了？- 你有看到迈克尔l吗？
- Hey, Joanna. How's Asher doing? - Have you seen Michael?
- 妈妈 妈妈 - 嘿
Mom! Mom! - Hey.
- 阿舍怎么样了？- 好消息
- How's Ash? Got some good news.
- 你弟弟会没事的 - 真的吗？
- Your brother's gonna be fine. - Really?
真的 没人能解释这一切 就象是奇迹一样
Yeah, really. No one can explain it. It's-It's a miracle.
他们还要让他留院观察一晚 之后他就可以回家了
They're gonna keep him overnight, but after that, he's coming home.
- 太好了 - 其他孩子怎么样了？
- That's great. - How are all the other kids doing?
也很好 很多近几天也可以出院了
Good. Real good. A bunch of them should be checking out in a few days.
特拉维斯医生说病房又要变得很安静了
Dr. Travis says the ward's gonna be like a ghost town.
特拉维斯医生？海德克尔医生呢？
Dr. Travis? What about Dr. Heidecker?
噢 他今天不在. - 一定是病了或是被什么耽误了
Oh, he wasn't in today.Must have been sick or something.
对 一定是这样
Yeah. Yeah, must have.
我走之后有发生什么事吗？
So did anything happen while l was gone?
没有 一切如常
No, same old stuff.
- 好的 你可以去看看阿舍了 - 现在吗？
- Okay. You can go see Ash. - Now?
只要你想去
Only if you want to.
我也得过去了 不然他就要自己发动车子走了
I better get going before he hot-wires the car and drives himself.
太糟糕了
It's too bad.
不 他们会没事的
Oh, they'll be fine.
我不是这个意思
That's not what l meant.
我是指迈克尔 他永远都会记得黑暗里有鬼怪存在的
I meant Michael. He'll always know there are things out there in the dark.
他不会和以前一样的 对吧？
Never be the same, you know?
有时候我真希望…
Sometimes I wish that...
什么？
What?
我希望我从不知道这些鬼怪的事情
I wish I could have that kind of innocence.
要是对你意味重大的话
If it means anything, sometimes
我也希望你从不知道
I wish you could too.